Thank you, and welcome to What's
谢谢 欢迎来到
New in Screen Recording and Live
屏幕录制和直播
Broadcast.
介绍会
My name is Johnny Trenh, I'm a
我叫 Johnny Trenh
software engineer at Apple
是苹果 ReplayKit 团队的
working on a ReplayKit team.
软件工程师
Today, my teammate Alexander
今天 我的同事
Subbotin and I are really
Alexander Subbotin 和我
excited to talk to you about all
非常高兴能和各位讲一讲
the new upcoming features we
今年我们为
have planned for ReplayKit this
ReplayKit 设计的新功能
We've got a lot to discuss, so
有很多要说的
let's go ahead and get started.
所以我们直接开始吧
ReplayKit is a framework that
ReplayKit 是一个框架
allows developers to record
让开发者可以
their applications audio, video,
把音频 视频
and microphone content to a
和麦克风内容
movie file that their users can
录制成电影文件
then review, edit, save, or
使得用户可以查看 编辑
share with the rest of the
保存或者分享
world.
给其他人
ReplayKit also supports Live
ReplayKit 同样也支持
Broadcast.
直播
For applications generating
对于 App 生成的内容
content, ReplayKit provides you
ReplayKit 提供
with all the tools necessary to
所有必要的工具
stream your application's audio,
来把 App 的音频
video, and microphone content to
视频和麦克风内容
a broadcast extension.
流式传输到直播扩展
For applications implementing a
对于执行了直播扩展
broadcast extension, ReplayKit
的 App 来说
comes equipped with easy to use
ReplayKit 有
Xcode templates that will help
简单的 Xcode 模板
your application stream
来帮助你的 App
ReplayKit content.
流式传输 ReplayKit 内容
ReplayKit records both audio and
ReplayKit 可以录制高清的
video in HD quality with
音频和视频
low-performance impact and
而且需要较小的性能损耗
minimal power usage.
和电量损耗
Privacy is a very big thing with
隐私对我们来说很重要
us, so both recording and
所以无论是录制
broadcasting comes equipped with
还是直播
privacy safeguards such as user
都有隐私保护措施
consent as well as all
例如用户许可
recordings and samples that
而且所有录制文件和样本
exclude system UI.
都有专属系统 UI
Since the release of ReplayKit,
自从 ReplayKit 发布
we have seen some amazing
我们从全世界的
adoption from developers all
开发者那里 看到很多
around the world.
很棒的应用
Applications like Galaxy on
一些 App 比如 Galaxy on Fire
Fire, Vainglory, Call of
Vainglory Call of Champions
Champions, and Modern Combat 5,
和 Modern Combat 5
are all using ReplayKit today to
都使用 ReplayKit
record and broadcast their
录制和
users' experiences with the rest
向世界各地直播
of the world.
其用户的体验
Last year we introduced Live
去年我们介绍了
Broadcast with ReplayKit.
ReplayKit 直播
And we are proud to say that
而我可以很骄傲地说
ReplayKit now powers some of the
现在移动流媒体中的
industry leaders in mobile
很多领军企业
streaming.
都在使用 ReplayKit
The support adoption and
我们的支持率 采用率
feedback we've received from
和从开发者那里得到的反馈
developers has been amazing.
都很棒
That is why this year we're
所以今年
really happy to introduce
我们很高兴能给你们介绍
ReplayKit 2.
ReplayKit 2
With ReplayKit 2, our goal is to
我们对 ReplayKit 2 的目标是
bring ReplayKit to every user
所有用户和 App 都可以
and every application.
使用 ReplayKit
We've designed our new features
我们设计了新的功能
to take ReplayKit beyond just
让 ReplayKit 不局限于
gaming, enabling all developers
游戏领域 让所有的开发者
to record and broadcast their
都可以录制
users' experiences to the whole
并向世界各地直播
world.
他们用户的体验
And to do that, the first thing
为了做到这一点
I want to talk about is In-App
首先 我要介绍
Screen Capture.
App 内屏幕捕捉
Look, we've already seen the
我们已经见识过
amazing content your users have
用户用 ReplayKit 做出的
been creating with ReplayKit.
非常好的内容
With ReplayKit 2, we're
在 ReplayKit 2 里
introducing In-App Screen
我们加入了 App 内屏幕捕捉
Capture, which is a powerful new
这个强大的新 API
API that's going to give you
让你可以
direct access to your
直接通过 ReplayKit
application's own audio, video,
访问 App 自己的
and microphone content straight
音频 视频
from ReplayKit.
和麦克风内容
Our goal with ReplayKit 2 was to
我们对 ReplayKit 2 的目标是
bring ReplayKit to every
让 ReplayKit 可以在所有 App 中
application.
使用
And to do that we're making
所以我们让
ReplayKit instantly available to
ReplayKit 现在适用于
every application on iOS.
iOS 的所有 App
Previously, to use ReplayKit and
以前 为了使用 ReplayKit
to have a application using
或者使用一个用
ReplayKit, you'd have to use our
ReplayKit 的 App 你必须要用
API.
我们的 API
But now, users can record and
但是现在 用户可以
broadcast their entire iOS
直接通过控制中心里的
screen experience straight from
屏幕录制按钮
the new screen recording control
录制并播出他们
found in Control Center.
整体 iOS 的屏幕体验
Also new with ReplayKit 2 is the
ReplayKit 2 还有一个创新
ability to pair your application
就是可以把 App 和
with a particular streaming
一个特定的流媒体服务
service.
配对
Developers can now seamlessly
开发者可以
integrate their entire streaming
从 App 内部
solution right from within their
完美地集合
own application.
整个流媒体解决方案
Last year, we introduced front
去年 我们提供了
camera support for ReplayKit.
ReplayKit 的前摄像头支持
This year with ReplayKit 2 we're
今年 在 ReplayKit 2 里
introducing Fast Camera
我们加入了快速镜头切换
Switching, which is going to
这样你就可以通过
enable you to use both the front
前摄像头和
and rear cameras for additional
后摄像头来添加
video commentary.
视频评论
We've got a lot of new and
有很多新的东西
exciting things to talk about.
要介绍
So, I'm just going to go ahead
所以让我们
and jump right in with In-App
直接开始说
Screen Capture.
App 内屏幕捕捉
powerful new API that's going to
是个强大的新 API
give you direct access to your
让你可以直接通过
application's own audio, video,
ReplayKit 访问
and microphone content straight
App 自己的音频视频
from ReplayKit.
和麦克风内容
This new API is going to open
这个新 API 可以让
doors to new user experiences
用户得到全新的体验
that just weren't possible
这在以前
before.
是做不到的
But, before we get into In-App
在介绍 App 内屏幕捕捉之前
Screen Capture, let's go ahead
让我们
and take a look at how
先来看一下
applications are currently using
现在 App 是如何用
ReplayKit to handle recording.
ReplayKit 录像的
An application that's currently
当前情况下
using ReplayKit will call in to
使用 ReplayKit 的 App
RPScreenRecorder to get the
会调入 RPScreenRecorder
shared recorder instance.
打开屏幕录制单例
From there, you'll call start
然后在屏幕录制单例
recording onto shared recorder
选择开始录制
instance, at which time the
这个时候
replay daemon will start to
回放 Daemon 程序会开始
capture your application's
捕捉 App 的
audio, video, and microphone
音频视频和麦克风内容
content, and create and manage a
为这个 App 专门
movie file just for your
创建并管理
application.
一个电影文件
When you call stop recording on
当你在屏幕录制单例
a shared recorder instance,
点击停止录制
replay daemon will communicate
回放 Daemon 程序会和
with a share and preview
分享和预览扩展沟通
extension and instantiate an
并实例化
RPPreviewViewController.
RPPreviewViewController
We'll pass that
我们会将
your application so that you can
传回给你的 App
present it to your users,
然后你才能展示给你的用户
allowing them to review, edit,
让他们查看 编辑
save, or share the recording
保存和分享
they just made in your
他们刚刚在你的 App 里
application.
录制的样本
With a new In-App Screen
使用新的 App 内屏幕捕捉功能
Capture, just like with
当你在录制时
recording, you're going to call
首先会调入
into RPScreenRecorder to get the
RPScreenRecorder
share recorder instance.
打开屏幕录制单例
From there, you'll call start
然后
capture on the share recorder
在屏幕录制单例
instance, at which point the
点击开始捕捉
replay daemon will start to
这时回放 Daemon 程序会
capture your application's
开始捕捉 App 的
audio, video, and microphone
音频视频和麦克风
content.
内容
But instead of creating and
替代了原来专门
managing a movie file just for
给你的 App 所创建和管理的
your application, ReplayKit will
一个电影文件
send those audio and video
ReplayKit 现在会把这些
samples right back up to
音视频样本 直接发回给
RPScreenRecorder.
RPScreenRecorder
A capture handler block is then
这时会调入一个捕捉处理器 Block
called, and we'll send the audio
我们会把音频和视频文件
and video samples, right back to
直接发送给
your application's process.
你的 App 进程
Your application now has direct
App 可以直接通过 ReplayKit
access to its own audio, video,
访问自己的
and microphone samples straight
音频视频和
from ReplayKit.
麦克风样本
Giving you direct access to your
直接从 ReplayKit
application's audio and video
访问 App 的
samples from ReplayKit will
音视频文件
provide you with more
可以让你
flexibility and control over the
更灵活也更好地掌控
content your users are already
用户创建的
creating.
内容
Just like with recording, In-App
和录制一样
Screen Capture captures audio
App 内屏幕捕捉
and video in HD quality, with
可以以较小的性能损耗
low-performance impact and
和电量损耗
minimal power usage.
捕捉到高清的音视频
Again, privacy is a very big
再重申一次
thing with us, so In-App Screen
我们很重视隐私
Capture comes equipped with
所以 App 内屏幕捕捉
privacy safeguards such as user
有隐私保护措施
consent as well as all samples
例如用户许可
excluding system UI.
和样本专用的系统 UI
The API is simple and
这个 API 很简单
lightweight.
也很小
So, let's go ahead and take a
那我们现在来
quick look at it.
快速看一下
StartCapture takes in two
StartCapture 有两个 Blocks
blocks, a captureHandler block
captureHandlerBlock
and a completionHandler block.
和 completionHandlerBlock
The captureHandler block is
每次 ReplayKit
called every time ReplayKit is
准备把样本送还给 App 时
ready to hand your application
captureHandlerBlock
back a sample.
都会被调用
We provide you with a
我们为你提供
CMSampleBuffer ref an
一个 CMSampleBuffer 参考
RPSampleBufferType and an NS
一个 RPSampleBufferType
Error.
和一个 NS Error
The completion handler block is
当 startCapture 完成时
called when startCapture has
completionHandlerBlock 被调用
completed and will give you an
并提供
NS Error indicating to you
NS Error 指示
whether or not an error has
startCapture 中
occurred during startCapture.
是否出现错误
The stopCapture also takes in a
stopCapture 也会调入
completionHandler which will
一个 completionHandler
also pass you back and NS Error
会回传给你 NS Error
indicating to you whether or not
为你指示 stopCapture 中
an error has occurred during
是否出现
stopCapture.
错误
Let's go ahead and take a look
让我们来看一下
at how we can use this in
实例中如何
practice.
操作
Here, in our example, what I
在我们这个例子里
want to do is I want to take the
我要把
samples that ReplayKit has given
ReplayKit 给我的样本
me and I want to use it to write
用 AVAssetWriter
a simple movie file to disc
将一个简单的电影文件
using AVAssetWriter.
写到盘里
So, here I have method called
有一个方法
didPressCaptureButton.
叫 didPressCaptureButton
Inside of it, I'm simply going
在里面
to grab the sharedRecorder
只要把屏幕录制单例
instance from RPScreenRecorder.
从 RPScreenRecorder 拿来
From there, I'll call
然后 调用 startCapture
startCapture providing it a
给它提供
capture handler block and a
captureHandlerBlock
completion handler block.
和 completionHandlerBlock
Remember, I'm trying to write a
还记得么 我要用 AVAssetWriter
movie file using AVAssetWriter
把我们拿到的样本
with the samples we get back.
写成电影文件
So it's really important for me
所以知道如何
to know how I'm going to handle
处理这些样本
these samples.
是很重要的
So, let's take a closer look at
让我们再来看一下
the capture handler.
captureHandler
Remember, the capture handler is
每次 ReplayKit 准备给 App
called every time ReplayKit is
传回一个样本时
ready to hand your application
captureHandler
back a sample.
都会被调用
We'll provide you with a
我们会为你提供
CMSampleBuffer ref, and
CMSampleBuffer 参考
RPSampleBufferType, and an NS
RPSampleBufferType
Error.
和 NS Error
Since I'm using these samples to
因为我要把这些样本
write a simple movie using
用 AVAssetWriter 写成
AVAssetWriter, it's really
简单的电影文件
important for me to know what
知道我从 ReplayKit
type of samples I'm getting back
得到的是哪种类型的样本
from ReplayKit.
是很重要的
Here we have a switch on
我们在
RPSampleType that's going to do
RPSampleType 这有个开关
just that.
可以做到这点
If I get a sample buffer type
如果有个 sampleBufferType
that's video, I'm simply going
是视频
to append that sample to my
只要把样本附加到
video input for my
AVAssetWriter
AVAssetWriter.
的视频输入
If I get a sample buffer type
如果有个 sampleBufferType
that's audio, I'll append that
是音频 只要把样本附加到
sample to my audio input for my
AVAssetWriter 的
AVAssetWriter.
音频输入
And finally, if I get a sample
最后 如果有个
buffer type that's for the
sampleBufferType
microphone, I'll append that
是麦克风 只要把样本附加到
sample to my microphone input
AVAssetWriter 的
for my AVAssetWriter.
麦克风输入
And, just like that, I am now
就像这样
handling all the expected types
我可以处理
of samples I'm going to get back
要从 ReplayKit 拿到的
from ReplayKit.
样本的所有类型
And I'm also using them to write
我还要用 AVAssetWriter
a simple movie to disc using
把他们写成一个简单的
AVAssetWriter.
电影文件到盘上
Let's go ahead and take a closer
让我们再来看一下
look at the completion handler.
completionHandler
Just like with recording, you
像录制一样
want to indicate to your users
我们希望用户知道
that a capture session has
捕捉进程
currently occurred or is in
已经开始 或者
session.
正在进行
So, in our completion handler,
所以在 completionHandler 里
we're going to simply call
我们调用
update the capture button with
updateCaptureButton
the error that we get back
带有我们从 completionHandler 中
during our completion handler.
得到的 error 代码
This will allow me to update my
这样我就可以更新 UI
UI and indicate to my users that
并且告诉我的用户
a capture session has occurred.
捕捉进程开始了
And that's it.
就这么简单
That's all you have to do to
这就是 要开始使用
start using this powerful new
这个强大的新 API 时
API.
要做的所有事情
I want to take a minute to
我们花点时间
revisit how In-App Screen
重温一下 App 内屏幕捕捉
Capture's actually working.
如何工作
And I'd like to remind you that
我想提醒你
your application now has direct
你的 App 现在可以
access to its own audio, video,
直接通过 ReplayKit
and microphone content straight
访问它自己的音频 视频
from ReplayKit.
和麦克风内容
In our example, we use these
在我们的例子里
samples to create a simple movie
我们用 AVAssetWriter 把这些样本
using AVAssetWriter, but you can
做成简单的电影文件
do so much more with this.
但其实你还可以做很多别的
Now that your application has
现在你的 App
access to its own audio and
可以访问自己的音频
video samples, you can create
和视频样本
and manage videos right into
你可以在在这个 App 里
your own application.
创建并管理视频
You can even create a custom
你甚至可以创建一个
video editor and have it
个性化视频编辑器
seamlessly integrated in the
并把它和
user experience for your
用户体验
application.
完美集合
Again, a goal of ReplayKit 2 was
再次重申  ReplayKit 2 的目标
to bring ReplayKit to every
是让 ReplayKit 适用所有的 App
application, not just gaming.
而不仅仅是游戏
Here, I have the same
我这有同一个
productivity app running on two
生产力 App
different iOS devices.
在两个不同 iOS 设备上运行
Now that I have access to my
我现在可以访问
application's audio and video
App 的音频
samples, just like with
和视频样本
broadcasts, I can encode these
像直播一样 我可以
samples myself, and I can send
自己编码这些样本
them to my own personal server.
并发送给我自己的服务器
From there, I can share my
我可以把 App 的
application's Screen Capture
屏幕捕捉
with any other instance of my
分享给
application running on any other
在其他设备上运行的
device.
App 的其他实例
This just wasn't possible
这在以前是不可能的
before, but it is now with
但现在 有了 App 间屏幕捕捉
In-App Screen Capture.
就可以了
These are just some of the
这些只是
examples of the new user
用 App 间屏幕捕捉
experiences you can create using
创建新用户体验的
In-App Screen Capture.
一些例子
We're really excited to see what
我们很希望看到
developers are going to do with
开发者们还有什么别的
it.
创新
With ReplayKit 2, our goal was
我们对 ReplayKit 2 的目标是
to bring ReplayKit to every type
让 ReplayKit 适用于所有 App
of application, not just gaming.
而不仅仅是游戏
And to do that, I'm really happy
因此
to introduce iOS Screen
我想介绍一下
Recording and Broadcast.
iOS 屏幕录制和直播
Broadcast is an amazing new user
是一个很棒的新的
feature that's going to allow
用户功能
users to record and broadcast
让用户可以录制和直播
their entire iOS screen
整个 iOS 屏幕体验
Let's go ahead and take a look
让我们来看看
at how we can use this new
如何使用
feature.
这个新功能
To use iOS Screen Recording and
要使用 iOS 屏幕录制和直播
Broadcast, you're going to first
首先要
need to enable the Screen
启用控制中心的
Recording control for Control
屏幕录制按钮
To do that, we're going to jump
我们直接进入
right into settings, and Control
设置
Center.
控制中心
From there we'll be shown all
我们可以看到
these supported controls for
所有控制中心的
Control Center.
支持按钮
We simply add the screen
只需要添加
recording control and we start
屏幕录制按钮
Control Center.
然后进入控制中心
And just like that, you're now
就这样
up and running ready to share
你现在已经可以
your entire iOS screen
分享整个
experience.
iOS 屏幕体验了
[applause] Thank you.
[ 鼓掌 ] 谢谢
To initiate an iOS screen
要开始 iOS 屏幕录制
recording, you simply tap the
只需要点击
Screen Recording control.
屏幕录制按钮
You are now recording your
你现在就在录制
entire iOS screen experience.
整个 iOS 屏幕体验了
That status bar and our screen
这个状态栏
recording control will indicate
和屏幕录制按钮
to you that a recording is
会通过显示录制指示器
ongoing by showing you recording
和当前录制的
indicator as well as the elapsed
运行时间
time for your current recording
告诉你
session.
现在正在录制
To stop the recording you simply
要停止录制
tap the screen recording control
你只需要再次点击
again.
屏幕录制按钮
When the recording has been
录制停止后
stopped, you'll be presented
会出现一个
with a notification indicating
通知 告诉你
to you that the screen recording
刚才录制的内容
you just took has now been saved
被保存到
in your Photos application.
相册里了
Tapping on this banner will take
点击这个横幅
you straight to your Photos
可以直接进入相册
application where you can
在那里你可以
review, edit, or share the
查看 编辑 或者分享
recording you just made.
刚刚录制的内容
You can also 3D Touch into our
你还可以 3D Touch
screen recording control which
屏幕录制按钮
will bring you straight to our
然后直接进入
expanded view where you'll have
扩展视图
access to the microphone
可以设置麦克风
settings as well as the ability
开始录制
to start recording, or to stop
或者停止录制
Now, let's say I've just
假设
downloaded a broadcast
我刚下载了一个
application that supports
直播 App
ReplayKit Live Streaming.
支持 ReplayKit 直播
And I'd like to use that
我想用这个
broadcast application to share
直播 App
my entire iOS screen experience.
分享我的完整 iOS 屏幕体验
Well, that's actually pretty
其实很简单
simple to do, because all you
你只需要
need to do is 3D Touch into our
3D Touch
screen recording control.
屏幕录制按钮
You'll be taken to our expanded
进入扩展视图
view, where all the applications
所有在此设备上
that are installed on your
安装的
device that currently support
支持 ReplayKit 直播
ReplayKit Live Streaming will be
的 App
shown.
都会显示
You simply need to select the
你只需要选择
service you'd like to use and
想要的服务
tap Start Broadcast.
然后点击开始直播
You are now broadcasting to the
你现在就在向
entire world your entire iOS
全世界直播
screen experience.
你的 iOS 屏幕体验
Just like with recording, the
和录制一样
status bar in the screen
屏幕录制按钮的
recording control will indicate
状态栏
to you that a broadcast is
会通过录制指示器
currently in session by showing
被选中的直播服务
you the recording indicator, the
和目前直播的时间
current selected broadcast
来显示
service, and the elapsed time
直播正在
for your current broadcast.
进行中
To stop the broadcast, you
要停止直播
simply tap the stop broadcast
只需要点击停止直播
button.
按键
Now, you can record a video to
现在 你可以录一个视频
teach your grandparents how to
教你的祖父母
make that FaceTime call.
如何用 FaceTime
You can even stream a video to
你甚至可以制作一个视频
teach your parents how to send
教你的父母
that important email.
怎么发送邮件
Or better yet, you can now
或者
record a video to teach your
你可以录一个视频
kids how to find their favorite
教你的孩子们怎么在 iTunes 里
TV shows and movies in iTunes.
找到他们喜欢的节目和电影
It has never been easier to
分享你完整的
share your entire iOS screen
iOS 屏幕体验
experience.
就是这么容易
iOS Screen Recording and
iOS 屏幕录制和直播
Broadcast creates new user
用使用 ReplayKit
experiences with applications
的 App
that are already using
创建新的
ReplayKit.
用户体验
So, let's take a quick minute to
让我们来看看
talk about some best practices.
一些很棒的实践
iOS Screen Recording and
当使用 ReplayKit 时
Broadcast has priority when it
iOS 屏幕录制和直播
comes to ReplayKit.
有优先权
So, if your application is
如果你的 App
currently using ReplayKit to
正在使用 ReplayKit
record or broadcast and the user
录制或者直播
initiates an iOS Screen
这时用户启动
Recording and Broadcast, your
iOS 屏幕录制和直播
application will be notified via
RPScreenRecorderDelegate
RPScreenRecorderDelegate that
会通知你的 App
your session has been
进程被
interrupted.
打断了
In this case, the recording will
在这种情况下
be discarded and you should
录制会被废弃
update your UI and notify the
你需要更新 UI
users accordingly.
并通知用户
iOS Screen Recording and
iOS 屏幕录制和直播
Broadcast is an amazing feature.
是个很好的功能
It's one that we hope users and
我们希望用户和
developers will use to create
开发者可以用它创造
new exciting iOS content.
更多新的 iOS 内容
And to help you do that, I'd
为了更好地帮助你们
like to bring Alexander Subbotin
Alexander Subbotin
up to the stage to talk to you a
会上台来
little bit more about how we do
和你们讲讲
broadcasting with ReplayKit.
如何用 ReplayKit 直播
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Thank you, Johnny.
>> 谢谢 Johnny
Good morning.
早上好
My name is Alexander Subbotin
我叫 Alexander Subbotin
and I am so excited to be here
很高兴能在这里
talk to you and share more
和你们分享
details about our Live Broadcast
我们直播 API 的
API.
更多细节
ReplayKit enables applications
ReplayKit 让 App
to stream their content to third
可以直接从
party broadcast services
你的 iOS 和 tvOS 设备
directly from your iOS and tvOS
把内容流式传输到
device.
第三方直播服务
On iOS you can also include
在 iOS 你可以用
voice and video commentary using
麦克风和相机
the microphone and the camera.
添加声音和视频评论
And all this content is
所有的内容都
absolutely secure and
很安全
unaccessible with a broadcast
并且无法从你使用的
service that you use.
直播服务访问
This is a high level picture of
这是一个直播如何工作的
how Live Broadcast really works.
高层图
All on the left, you see a
左边
player who at some point wants
一个玩家想
to broadcast his game Tower Dash
把他的游戏 Tower Dash
to Mobcrush which is a broadcast
在叫 Mobcrush 的直播服务中
service.
直播
So Tower Dash communicates to
Tower Dash 与
the ReplayKit API to initiate
ReplayKit API 沟通
the broadcast.
开启直播
And once that happens, ReplayKit
一旦开启
will present some UI that allows
ReplayKit 会呈现一些 UI
user to ping the broadcast
让用户可以 ping 命令
service.
直播服务
And that would be Mobcrush for
在这里就是
us.
Mobcrush
And the broadcast starts.
直播开始了
And once broadcast is running,
直播进行时
ReplayKit will be providing
ReplayKit 会把
audio and video samples to the
音频和视频样本
mob crush app extension that
提供给 Mobcrush App 扩展
directly talks to the broadcast
它可以直接对接
service and the viewers around
直播服务和
the world can watch the
在网上看直播的
livestream online.
全世界的观众
This is just a picture of how
这就是一个如何实现直播
broadcast runs.
的图例
And the way I want to describe
我想把它
it to all of you is, I want to
分成几个部分
break it into parts because if
来给你们讲解
you are a client application
因为如果你是客户端 App 开发员
developer, game developer the
或者是游戏开发员
only thing you need to do is to
你只需要
present some ViewController
提供一些 ViewController
initiate broadcast and couple of
开启直播
other fairly simple steps.
和几个其他简单的步骤
But I also know that some of you
但是我知道
in this room broadcast service
这个屋子里的有些人是
developers.
直播服务开发员
And we are going to walk through
所以我会
the process for you and talk
讲解整个步骤
about how do you actually
告诉你如何
implement those extensions.
实现这些扩展
So, starting with the client
首先从客户端开始
side and what the client
客户端 App
application wants to do, for
都要做什么
that we have a fairly simple API
我们有一个简单的 API
that really wrapped up in those
包含在
three classes.
这三个类里
There's
包括
BroadcastActivityViewController
BroadcastActivityViewController
and this class is used to
这个类是用来
initiate a broadcast and it
发起直播
presents this built in UI where
并显示这个 built UI
you select the broadcast
让你可以选择
service.
直播服务
RPBroadcastController allows you
RPBroadcastController
to manage the broadcast in your
让你可以在代码里管理直播
code and you would usually wire
你可以连接到 UI
to some UI where user can start,
使得用户可以
stop, pause, or resume the
开始 停止 暂停 或者恢复
broadcast.
直播
And the
另外
RPBroadcastControllerDelegate is
RPBroadcastControllerDelegate
internal and this is a dedicated
是内部的
[inaudible] part about different
是直播中不同事件的
events during the broadcast.
专用的部分
The broadcast can stop for some
直播有可能会停止
reason, there could be an error,
可能发生错误
or the broadcast extension may
或者直播扩展
want to pass some information to
要给客户端 App 提供
the client app, and this is
一些信息
where the delegate tells the
这时 delegate 就会告诉
user.
用户
And now, I'm going to stop here
那么 这部分
talking about this part of the
我就不多讲了
picture because last year,
因为去年
we covered this API in depth in
在 ReplayKit 直播课程里
our session Go Live with
我们深入地讲解了
ReplayKit.
这个 API
So, in case you have not adopted
如果你还没有采用这个 API
the API yet, please go to the
请到 App 里
app and you can find the link to
找到去年课程的链接
last year's session and learn
那里可以了解更多
more about that developer API.
关于这个开发者 API 的内容
Now let's talk about the second
现在我们来说一说
part of the equation, you have
方程式中第二个部分
developer of the broadcast
直播服务的
service.
开发者
How do you integrate your
如何集成你的服务
service so that you could stream
使得你可以流式传输
the content created by all these
玩家 游戏
players, games, and other
和其他 App 创造的
applications?
内容
And the answer is these three
答案就是
extensions.
这三个扩展
The first one on the top is what
第一个是
we call Broadcast Setup
Broadcast Setup 扩展
extension, and its purpose is to
它会显示
present some UI where you can
一些 UI
ask user to enter some
让用户输入
information, you may want user
信息
to give the broadcast a
你可能想让用户
particular name or maybe log in
给直播命名
credentials or any details that
输入凭证
you need fire up your broadcast.
或者其他一些细节
And the second one is called
第二个是
Broadcast Upload extension.
Broadcast Upload 扩展
And the function of this
这个扩展的功能是
extension is to receive the
接收 ReplayKit 提供的
media samples handed by
媒体样本
ReplayKit and encode them,
并编码
create a video stream, and
创建一个视频流
upload to the online service.
并上载到线上服务
Each extension is a separate
每个扩展都是
binary that is installed on your
和直播 App 同时
device along with the broadcast
安装在你的设备上的
app.
分别的二进制
So you can install to Mobcrush,
你可以安装到 Mobcrush
you also get setup extension and
你也可以把 Setup 扩展
upload extension installed on
和 Upload 扩展
your device.
安装在你的设备上
And each extension runs in its
每个扩展
own process independently from
独立于 Mobcrush
Mobcrush that contains
运行自己的进程
extensions and Tower Dash that
包含扩展和 Tower Dash
initiates the broadcast.
来发起直播
So usually these are three
一般来说有三个进程
processes and the process of the
Mobcrush 的包容 App
containing app of the Mobcrush
的进程
is never launched.
从未被启用
And to help you get started
为了帮助你开始
developing new broadcast
开发新的直播扩展
extensions, we provide very easy
我们给这两种扩展都
to use Xcode templates for both
提供很简单的
types of extensions.
Xcode 模板
And just add two extensions to
只需要给 Xcode 工程
your Xcode project and you are
添加两个扩展
ready to begin.
就好了
And now let's talk about how you
现在来讲讲
actually code all of this.
具体如何编码
Starting from the setup
从 Setup 扩展
extension.
开始
As I said, the purpose of the
我刚才说过
setup extension is to present
Setup 扩展的目的是
this UI for user can enter the
显示 UI
name of the broadcast or
让用户输入直播的名字
something.
或其他内容
But it also has another
但是它还有另外一个
important function.
重要的功能
It can get some information
它可以获取
about the client application
客户 App 的一些重要信息
such as a bundleID, the name of
比如 BundleID
the application, or the icon of
App 的名字
the application.
和图标
And it can upload this
它可以上载这些信息
information to the broadcast
到直播服务
service so that the broadcast
这样直播服务
service could build an
就可以给观众
experience for viewers when the
创建一个体验
viewer comes to the website and
当用户登上网站时
he knows here's this place where
他知道
everyone playing Tower Dash,
这是大家玩 Tower Dash 的地方
there's an icon of Tower Dash.
有 Tower Dash 的图标
And although the extension can
尽管这个扩展
request from the broadcast
可以从直播服务
service a URL of that particular
申请一个在网站上
Live Broadcast happening on the
直播的 URL
website, and share it back to
并重新分享给 App
the application so that the
这样玩家就可以
player could send it to his
发送给朋友
friends and get more followers.
并获得更多关注
The ViewController that
执行这个 UI 的
implements this UI communicates
ViewController
to ReplayKit using property
用一个叫 extensionContext 的属性
called extensionContext.
和 ReplayKit 沟通
And the class of this property
这个属性的类
is a category of
是 NSExtensionContext
NSExtensionContext that has two
的一个分类
more functions added by
还有两个由 ReplayKit
ReplayKit.
添加的功能
The first one is
第一个是
loadBroadcastingApplicationInfo
loadBroadcastingApplicationInfo
and the second one is
第二个是
completeRequest with
completeRequest 带有
broadcastURL and setupInfo.
broadcastURL 和 setupInfo
The first one as I said it's
第一个
used to get the icon and the
用来获取
name of the application, and
App 的名字和图标
here is a small code example of
这有一个例子
how you could do that and pass
告诉你们如何做
this information to the
并把信息传递给
broadcast session.
直播进程
The broadcast service when it
直播服务
has this information, it can
得到这些信息时
identify in the broadcast
就可以识别直播进程
sessions, create channels, and
创建通道
build simple intuitive user
创造像这样
experience of viewers experience
简单而直观的
like this.
用户体验
The viewer comes to the app and
观众到 App 上
he has an icon and name of the
可以看到 App 的
application.
图标和名字
So, when you're done uploading
当你上载完这个图标
this icon, and already collected
并收集了所有
all the information that you
开始直播
need to begin the broadcast, you
所需信息之后
should call the second one
就该调入第二个
called completeRequest with
completeRequest 带有
broadcastURL and setupInfo.
broadcastURL 和 setupInfo
The broadcastURL will be
broadcastURL
available to the client
对客户端 App 来说
application as a property of the
可以作为
broadcast controller and the
broadcastController 的属性
setupInfo it's a dictionary that
setupInfo 是你在扩展中
you create inside this extension
创建的一个字典
and all the information you
当直播开始时
collected from the user, you put
所有从用户那
it to that dictionary, and it
收集到的信息
will be passed to the upload
都放进字典
extension when the broadcast
并传送至上载扩展
You should also always provide
你应该随时给
an option for the user to cancel
用户提供
broadcast, and for that you just
停止直播的选项
use your regular old
你只需要用以前的
cancelRequest method of the
extensionContext 的
extensionContext.
cancelRequest 方法
Now, let's talk about the upload
现在我们讲讲
extension.
Upload 扩展
As I said, it's function is to
我说过 它的功能是
receive the media frames handed
接收 ReplayKit 实时传送的
by ReplayKit in real time,
媒体信息
encode them, create a video
编码 创建一个视频流
stream, and upload it to the
并上载到
broadcast service.
直播服务
If you create a new upload
如果你用 Xcode 模板
extension using Xcode templates,
创新一个新的 Upload 扩展
you will find a sampleHandler
你会在你的 Xcode project 里
class like this in your Xcode
发现一个这样的
project, and this is where you
sampleHandler 类
override functions that take
它可以重写一些功能
care of events like the
管理
broadcast has started, stopped,
直播开始 停止
paused, or resumed.
暂停或者恢复
And also the function called
还有一个功能叫
processSampleBuffer, now this is
processSampleBuffer
the one that you want to
要管理
override to handle incoming
引入的媒体样本
media samples.
就要重写它
This is where all the magic
这就是最
happens.
奇妙的地方
You upload, the encoding, and
你在这里编码
uploading here.
和上载
So, when the broadcast starts,
当直播开始时
ReplayKit notifies extension
ReplayKit 通知扩展
that it will begin providing it
要向它提供
with media samples and ReplayKit
媒体样本
is using the function called
ReplayKit 使用一个叫
broadcastStarted with setupInfo
broadcastStarted with setupInfo
of this.
的功能来完成这个
And here's a code example that
这有个例子告诉你
shows you that you do receive a
你接收到一个 setupInfo
setupInfo as an argument of that
作为功能的变元
function, and you could extract
你可以从字典里
say, name of the broadcast from
提取直播的名字
the dictionary and pass it to
并传输到
the broadcast session, or in
直播进程
case a broadcast has started
或者 万一直播从已经
from the Control Center you can
控制中心开始了
just let know the session about
你可以让直播进程
this one.
知道这一点
And now, let me zoom in on the
现在 我们来了解一下
processSampleBuffer function.
processSampleBuffer 功能
ReplayKit provides extension
ReplayKit 给扩展
with three types of the media
提供三种类型的
samples.
媒体样本
Video samples captured from the
从屏幕捕捉的
screen.
视频样本
Audio samples captured from the
从 App 捕捉的音频样本
application, this is the audio
这就是你的 App 刚刚
your application's playing back
直播的
right now.
音频样本
And the audio samples captured
还有从麦克风捕捉的
And you can use any technology
你可以使用任意一种技术
to encode this media, but as a
来编码这个媒体
practical matter we provide you
但是为了更实用
a lower level API called
我们提供一个低级 API
VideoToolbox.
叫 VideoToolbox
This is a framework that
它是一个框架
provides access to the hardware
让硬件可以
accelerated encoding and
加速编码
decoding.
和解码
All samples go to the upload
所有的样本都去到
extension and handled by the
Upload 扩展
function processSampleBuffer.
被 processSampleBuffer 功能管理
And the function should encode
这个功能会编码
and upload the media samples.
并上载媒体样本
Here in this code example, we
在这个例子里
show you how you could use a
我们要告诉你如何用
VideoToolbox to encode the video
VideoToolbox 来编码
sample.
视频样本
In your real code, you would
在实际代码中
also have to implement the call
你还需要执行回叫
back to receive the encoded
来接收编码数据
data, et cetera.
等等
But here I would like to speak
但是在这 我想说一下
about the VideoToolbox, because
VideoToolbox
it's especially important when
因为它对你在 App 扩展中
you do your video processing in
进行视频处理时
an app extension.
非常重要
Because app extensions have much
因为 App 扩展
lower memory limits compared to
跟编程 App 比
the programmed applications.
内存限制低很多
And having access to this
能够有硬件
hardware accelerated video
快速视频编码
encoding is vital for the
对 ReplayKit 上载扩展
ReplayKit upload extensions.
非常重要
And this year, we have great
今年 有一个好消息
news, VideoToolbox is also
VideoToolbox 现在
available on tvOS now.
也可以在 tvOS 使用
So, you can build highly
所以 你为两个平台
optimized, very efficient
都可以创建
extensions for both platforms.
优化的高效的扩展
This is a high level picture of
这是一个关于
how Live Broadcast works, and
直播如何运作的高层图
who implements each part.
谁执行哪个部分
Again if you are a game
如果你是游戏开发员
developer, client application
或者客户端 App 开发员
developer, all you need to worry
你只需要考虑
about is just present the
展示 ViewController
ViewController initiate and stop
开始或者停止
the broadcast, and you could
直播
implement this API and be done
你可以执行这个 API
by the end of this session.
并等进程结束就好了
And if you are a broadcast
如果你是
service developer there's a
直播服务开发员
little more work on your side.
你要做的更多一点
You need to receive the samples,
你需要接收这些样本
encode them, and upload to the
编码它们 并上载到
broadcast service.
直播服务
There's one more thing I need to
结束这部分之前
go over before we finish with
还有一点
this part of the talk.
需要讲一讲
Is that so far we've been
到目前为止
assuming that all the data flows
我们都假设所有的数据
upwards from the application to
都从 App 流向
the online service, but indeed
线上服务
it is also possible for the data
但是其实也有可能
to be flowing back from the
数据会从线上服务
online service to the
流回到
application.
App
And that could be some viewers
它可以是观众的反馈
feedback, like the comments of
比如观众的评论
the viewers or likes, or any
或者点赞
kind of data number viewers.
或者其他任何数据
And for that we provide an API
为此 我们提供一个 API
that helps you to deliver this
帮助你从扩展中
information from the extension
把这些信息
to the client application.
传输到客户 App
And you have to just put this
你只需要把这些数据
data in a dictionary and use the
放到字典里
function called
并从你的扩展中
updateServiceInfo from within
使用这个叫
your extension.
updateServiceInfo 的功能
And that dictionary would be
这个字典
available to the application as
对 App 来说可以当作
a property of the broadcast
broadcastController 的
controller.
一个属性
The name of the property is
这个属性的名字叫
serviceInfo and it's KVO
serviceInfo
observable, so you can monitor
而且是可以通过 KVO 观察的
this and update the UI
所以你可以监控并适时的
appropriately.
更新 UI
This is it for the Live
这就是关于直播 API
Broadcast API overview.
的全部
And having all this information
用这些信息
you can build absolutely new
你可以创建新的
products, given that you also
产品
construct the broadcast from the
如果你从控制中心
Control Center you can build
创建了直播
third parties screen mirroring
你就可以创建第三方屏幕镜像
or video share, sharing of the
视频分享
screen during the video
或者在视频会议中
conference.
分享屏幕
Thank you, and please come,
谢谢
please welcome Johnny back on
有请 Johnny 回到
stage.
台上
[ Applause ]
[ 鼓掌 ]
>> Thank you, Alexander.
>> 谢谢 Alexander
So, as Alexander has just
就像 Alexander 说的
stated, current broadcaster
现在的直播 App
application, you would need to
你需要
present to the user a
给用户提供一个
RPBroadcastActivity
RPBroadcastActivityViewController
ViewController that allows them
让他们选择
to choose a public service to
一个公共服务
broadcast your application to.
来直播你的 App
Well, sometimes you don't want
有的时候也许
to broadcast your application to
你不想把你的 App
a public service.
直播到公共服务
Sometimes, you want your
有的时候 你希望
application to use your
你的 App 使用
broadcasting service.
你的直播服务
Well, with ReplayKit 2 and
用 ReplayKit 2
Broadcast Pairing, you can do
和直播配对
just that.
你可以做到
Broadcast Pairing enables you to
直播配对让你可以
fully and seamlessly integrate
完全在你的 App 里
your entire streaming solution,
完美地集合
all from within your own
你的整个
application.
流媒体解决方案
Here we have our budget
我们这有
application and we have our
预算 App
conference application that
和会议 App
supports ReplayKit Live
支持 ReplayKit 直播
Streaming and has implemented a
并执行了
broadcast extension.
一个直播扩展
I want our budget application to
我想要把预算 App
stream exclusively to our
单独流式传输到
conference application's
会议 App 的
broadcast extension.
直播扩展
So to do that, I'm going to
因此 我要开启
initiate a broadcast pair.
直播配对
Our budget application is going
预算 App 要
to call load with preferred
在 RPActivityViewController 类
extension on the class
加载
RPActivityViewController.
优先的扩展
We'll get back an instance of
我们会从
RPBroadcastActivity
RPBroadcastActivityViewController
ViewController much like we do
得到一个实例
with general broadcast
和一般直播开启
initiation, but here is the main
差不多
difference between Broadcast
但这是直播配对和
Pairing and general broadcast
一般的直播开始
initiation.
的主要区别
Because when you go and present
因为当你
that ViewController, instead of
展示 ViewController 时
the user being presented with a
用户不再会
picker that allows them to
看到一个选项
choose a public service, they'll
让他们选择一个公共服务
be presented with an alert that
而是会看到一个提示
indicates to them your
告诉他们
application's intent to use a
你的 App 要用
particular broadcast service.
某个特定的直播服务
Here, our budget application
在这里 预算 App
wants to stream to our
想要流式传输到
conference application's
会议 App 的
broadcast service.
直播服务
When a user taps accept,
当用户选择同意
ReplayKit will immediately
ReplayKit 会立刻
launch the paired broadcast
开启配对直播扩展
extension allowing the user to
让用户输入
input any information that might
任何对直播进程
be important to the broadcasting
很重要的
session.
信息
When the user has finished
当用户输入完
inputting all their information,
信息后
ReplayKit will start
ReplayKit 会开始
broadcasting to the paired
对配对直播扩展
broadcast extension.
进行直播
And just like that, our budget
就这样 预算 App
application is now streaming
现在就在
exclusively to its paired
单独流式传输到
broadcast extension.
它的配对直播扩展
Let's go ahead and take a look
让我们来看看
at the API for Broadcast
直播配对 API
very simple.
很简单
It's a new class method on
它是
RPBroadcastActivity
RPBroadcastActivityViewController
ViewController called
的一个新类方法
load(withPreferredExtension.
叫 loadwithPreferredExtension
We'll hand you back an instance
我们会给你提供一个
of
broadcastActivityViewController
broadcastActivityViewController
的实例
that you can then present to
用来展示给
your users.
你的用户
Let's jump in and take a look at
让我们直接来看一下
how our budget application is
关于如何让预算 App
going to imitate a broadcast
仿效
pair in a little bit more
直播配对
detail.
的更多细节
Here, I have a method called
这有个方法
didPressBroadcastPairButton.
叫 didPressBroadcastPairButton
Inside of it, I'm simply going
在里面
to call
我只需要
load(withPreferredExtension: on
在 RPBroadcastActivity ViewController 类
the class RPBroadcastActivity
调入
ViewController.
LoadwithPreferredExtension
We'll go ahead and get back an
我们会得到一个
instance of RPBroadcastActivity
RPBroadcastActivityViewController
ViewController that.
的实例
When we go ahead and present the
当我们
user be presented with an alert
给用户显示一个提醒
that indicates to them my
告诉他们
application's intent to use a
我的 App 希望使用
particular broadcasting service.
某一个特定的直播服务时
Once the user accepts, ReplayKit
一旦用户同意
will handle the rest and we'll
ReplayKit 会处理剩下的事情
the broadcasting extension
并开启配对的
that's been paired.
直播扩展
Broadcast Pairing has been
直播配对
designed so that the
是为了让
broadcasting app and the
直播 App
broadcasting service are tightly
和直播服务
coupled.
紧密配对
So, initiating a Broadcast
所以开启一个
Pairing session, developers are
直播配对进程
going to have to supply a
开发者要提供
bundleID for the broadcast
一个 bundleID
extension.
给直播扩展
Users will also need to accept
用户也需要
the broadcasting pair through
通过提示同意直播配对
the alert, which will be shown
每次当你想开启
every time you wish to initiate
直播配对进程时
a Broadcasting Pair session.
提示都会出现
Broadcast Pairing allows you to
直播配对让你可以
seamlessly integrate your entire
在你的 App 里
streaming solution all within
完美集合你的
your own application.
整个流媒体解决方案
Now, we know that creating
我们现在知道了
replays and Live Streams with
以用户评论录制回放和直播
user commentary is a fantastic
对于吸引新用户
way to get new user engagement
到你的 App
in your application as well as
和围绕 App
generating a community around
创建一个社区
your application.
是非常有用的
That's why last year we
这是为什么 去年我们
introduced front camera support
引入了 ReplayKit
for ReplayKit.
前置摄像头支持
And which is why this year we're
这也是为什么 今年
also introducing Fast Camera
我们为 ReplayKit 2 引入了
Switching for ReplayKit 2.
快速摄像头转换
Fast Camera Switching allows you
这让你可以在
to change the camera feed in the
RPScreenRecorder 的
camera preview view found in
cameraPreviewView 里
RPScreenRecorder to use either
改变摄像头来源
the front camera or the rear
选择前置摄像头或者
camera.
后置摄像头
The camera preview view found in
RPScreenRecorder 里的
RPScreenRecorder is a subclass
cameraPreviewView
of UIView, so it can be added to
是 UIView 的一个子类
just about any application.
所以可以添加到几乎任何 App
Developers are responsible for
开发者要负责
UI elements that allow the user
让用户调出或者取消
to present and dismiss the
cameraPreviewViewcamera
camera preview view, as well as
的 UI 元素
UI elements to allow the user to
以及让用户转换
switch the camera preview view.
cameraPreviewView 的UI元素
Let's go ahead and take a quick
让我们看一看
look at the API for Fast Camera
快速摄像头转换
Switching.
的 API
Switching is really simple.
的 API 很简单
It consists of a new property on
它包含 RPScreenRecorder 里的
RPScreenRecorder called
一个新的属性
cameraPosition, which is used to
叫 cameraPosition
note the current cameraPosition
用来记录 sharedRecorder 单例
for the sharedRecorder instance.
的目前摄像头位置
CameraPosition is an enumeration
CameraPosition 是一个
RPCameraPosition which includes
列举 RPCameraPosition
RPCameraPosition front and
包含 RPCameraPosition front
RPCameraPosition back which is
和 RPCameraPosition back
used for the front and back
分别用于前置摄像头
cameras respectively.
和后置摄像头
Let's go ahead and jump into an
现在我们直接通过
example of how we can start
一个例子来看一下 如何开始
using Fast Camera Switching.
使用快速摄像头转换
Wow, that photo looked a lot
看 照片在小屏幕上
better on a smaller screen.
看起来好多了
Here, we have a function called
我们这有一个功能
showPreviewView.
叫 showPreviewView
Inside we're simply going to
在里面 我们只需要
grab this sharedRecorder
在 RPScreenRecorder
instance on RPScreenRecorder.
抓取这个 sharedRecorder 单例
From there, I'll grab the
然后 我要从
cameraPreviewView for the RP,
sharedRecorder 单例
for the sharedRecorder instance.
抓取 cameraPreviewView
Since the sharedRecorder
因为 sharedRecorder 单例
instance and its cameraView is a
和它的 cameraView
subclass of UI view, I'm simply
是 UIView 的一个子类
going to add it as a subview to
我只要把把它作为 subview
my view in my application.
添加到我 App 的 view 里
And just like that, we're now
就这样 我们现在
using the cameraPreviewView and
在使用 cameraPreviewView
the front facing camera for our
和前摄像头
video commentary.
来录制视频评论
Let's go ahead and take a quick
现在让我们看看
look at how we can use Fast
如何使用
Camera Switching.
快速摄像头转换
Here, I have a method called
有一个方法
didPressCameraSwitch.
叫 didPressCameraSwitch
Again, I'm simply going to grab
再一次 我要从
a sharedRecorder instance from
RPScreenRecorder 抓取
our RPScreenRecorder.
sharedRecorder 单例
I'm really interested in knowing
我很想知道
what the current cameraPosition
现在的 cameraPosition
is.
是什么
So, in our method here, we're
在我们的这个方法里
going to check to see what the
我们要看一下
current cameraPosition is.
现在的 cameraPosition 是什么
And whatever it is, I'm going to
无论是什么
switch it to its opposite.
我都要把它换成相反的
So here, We notice that our
我们可以看到
cameraPosition for our
sharedRecorder 的
sharedRecorder is using
cameraPosition 使用的是
RPCameraPosition.front.
RPCameraPosition.front
I'm simply going to set the
只需要把
shareRecorder's cameraPosition
shareRecorder 的 cameraPosition
to be RPCameraPosition.back.
设为 RPCameraPosition.back
And just like that, our preview
这样 我们的 PreviewView
view is now using the rear
使用的就是
camera for its video commentary.
后摄像头了
It really is just that easy and
就这么容易
it really is just that fast.
这么快
Fast Camera Switching will give
快速摄像头转换
you additional tools to provide
让你可以给用户提供
your users with to create more
更多的工具
engaging video commentary in the
让他们可以用
content their creating in your
在你的 App 里制作的内容
application.
来创造更多的视频评论
We have covered a lot today.
我们今天讲了很多
So let's go ahead and take a
所以让我们来
minute to recap.
回顾一下
In ReplayKit 2, we introduced
在 ReplayKit 2 里
In-App Screen Capture, which is
我们介绍了 App 内视频捕捉
a powerful new API that's going
是一个强大的新 API
to give you direct access to
让你可以直接
your application's own audio,
从 ReplayKit 访问
video, and microphone content
你的 App 的音频
straight from ReplayKit.
视频和麦克风内容
With iOS Screen Recording and
用 iOS 屏幕录制和直播
Broadcast, users can now record
用户可以直接从
and broadcast their entire iOS
控制中心
screen experience straight from
录制和直播他们的整个
Control Center.
iOS 屏幕体验
We introduced Broadcast Pairing
我们介绍了直播配对
which enable you to seamlessly
让你可以在自己的 App 里
integrate your entire streaming
集合整个
solution all within your own
流媒体解决方案
And finally, with Fast Camera
最后 用快速摄像头转换
Switching you now have more
你将有更多的工具
tools to provide your users with
提供给你的用户
to create more engaging video
来创造更多吸引人的
commentary.
视频评论
For more information about our
想了解更多关于今天课程的内容
session today, visit us at
请访问
developer.apple.com.
developer.apple.com
We are session 606.
我们是第 606 课程
We hope you have a wonderful
希望你们享受
WWDC.
WWDC
Thank you.
谢谢